U.S. Manpower Administration "Manpower Daily Reporter" Newsletters 5380
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- November, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 20, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 19, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 18, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 17, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 14, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 13, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 12, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 10, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday November 7, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday November 6, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday November 5, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday November 4, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday November 3, 1969. Item is in English.
- December, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 23, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 22, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 19, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 18, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday December 17, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 16, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 15, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 12, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 11, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday December 10, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 9, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 8, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday December 5, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday December 4, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday December 2, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday December 1, 1969. Item is in English.
- January, 1970; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 30, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 29, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 28, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 27, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 26, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 23, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 22, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 21, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 20, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 19, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 16, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 15, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 14, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 13, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 12, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 9, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday January 8, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday January 7, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday January 6, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday January 5, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Friday January 2, 1970. Item is in English.
- February, 1970; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Thursday February 5, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Wednesday February 4, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Tuesday February 3, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Manpower Daily Reporter, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Monday February 2, 1970. Item is in English.
- March, 1970; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Daily Manpower Reporter discontinued, Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
    By Office of Manpower Policy, Evaluation and Research. Post card dated March 25, 1970. Item is in English.